平衡与升进
In the history of humanity in the history of evoluntion in the history of spirituality
在人类的历史 在进化的历史 在灵性的历史
It's the most important time
这是一个最重要的时刻
because here where you get what heaven has been promised to you so far
因为在这里你会获得上天给你的承诺
our planet is moving in a spiral way, all the planets are moving in a spiral way
地球行进在一个螺旋的轨道，所有的行星正在运行在螺旋的轨道
and they are creating all possible things
并且它们创造所有合适的事情
for the use of human beings so they can save time
为了人类的使用 他们会节省时间
save time for getting their ascent and for meditating
为了他们的升进和静坐成长节省时间
growth, this is the right side and this is the left sid
这是右边 这是左边
This is the left sympathetic nervous system say, and this is the right sympathetic nervous system
这是左交感神经系统 这是右交感神经系统
and really spinal cord look like this and inside here is the spinal cord
并且脊髓看上去像这样 在这里面是脊髓
which has these centers in it, subtle centers
这些中心在这里面 精微的中心
Now when you start using energy of the centers, say, too much of the right
当你开始使用这些中心的能量 太多右面的
and you start moving more toward to the right and there is a constriction
你开始移向右面 那地方产生压力
and the power becomes less because you are exhausted going more to the right side
并能量变弱因为你过度的移向右脉
suddenly something happens and from the left there is a jerk
忽然某些事发生了 从左边那产生筋挛
then the connection is completely broken. This is on its own. It start working on its own.
然后连接被完全的破坏了 它是它自己 它开始自己工作
that's we can say that it has become malignant
我们可以说它成为恶性的
have no relationship with the whole
没有了和整体的联系
to have propotionate growth so if the nose starts growing it can cover your eyes
没有成比例的成长 所以如果鼻子成长 它可以覆盖你的眼睛
cover you mouth everyting. it is how the cancer is settling in
覆盖你的嘴 每一样东西 这就是癌症怎样的形成
的
or any other disease so many psychosomatic diseases
或者其他的任何疾病如此多的身心病
are nothing but, somatic is from the right side
不是其他 躯体来自右边
and when the psychic gives in, it becomes a psychosomatic disease
当灵魂让步 成为身心病
There are so many diseases which are more psychosomatic than physical
有如此多的疾病 身心病多于身体上的疾病
and these we call them as incurable
那些我们称为不治之症
can be easily cured by Kundalini awakening.
可以很简单的通过昆达里尼唤醒得以医治
because when Kundalini passes through this
因为当昆达里尼通过
It just integrates them. For example she is going like this
它整合它们 例如 她如此通过
And she goes into this, integrates them
她进入这 整合它们
Just like she strings them, and also she nurishes these centers
就像她串起它们，并且她也滋养这些中心
That's how people get cured, automatically by themselves by their own power.
那是人们如何得到医治 自动的被他们自己医治 被自身的力量医治